We're supposed to be things
that act and not to be
acted upon If we start using
AI too much then AI starts
using us and that should
be the other way around
give it a baseline.
Like, here's what I'm thinking.
Is there something wrong
with what I'm thinking?
How could this be improved?
I think like people coming
into the lab in a semester
when things have been
built, and they're just kind
of like, I never got the
chance to learn any of this.
Claude has been
controlling the whole thing
writing the code that does the tests and
running the tests The scary part of that
is I have not done that
and I don't currently
know like if you asked me to do it myself
I couldn't do it right now it would take
me a couple days probably that's scary
that's one of the limits I
think that AI has is it's
not very good at generating
those structures that
we need.
Yeah, like generating images
and like spatial awareness
AI is very poor at.
It does really well with
like analyzing information
and like things to do with
like words and things like
that.
It goes very good at image
analysis, spatial analysis,
things like that.
It's not there.
Yeah, it doesn't live in the three.
world with us.
It's all just code and stuff.
I'm just wondering, would
it be helpful, like when
new people come into the lab,
we would run them through,
hey, this is good ways to be using AI?
like using it to teach
you to do things and using
it to maybe like debug
stuff like we need some kind
of like tutorial to show people
Yeah, I like that, Audrey.
That gets me thinking, we
can probably pull some of
the things from this discussion.
I think I can add, probably
add this in with one of
those kind of like onboarding things.
Or maybe I missed heard
Audrey, but I think I heard
her say real.
So like, you know, we could
make like a real of us
like being, this is good.
this is bad
Okay, we'll probably call it good there.
Thanks, Audrey Carl, everybody.